Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Charles Everett Colcord, January 23, 1984
  American Radio Association; Port Security Act.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-041 - OH-01-043)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-041 - OH-01-043, Box 23, Audiocassette 27A - 27B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 35, Audiocassette 27A - 27B)
- Roger Cole, undated
  General note
  Release form Yes
- Mabel Collie, October 21, 1990
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-044)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-044, Box 31, Audiocassette 173)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 173)
- Sharon Collie, October 24, 1990
  Mt. Sinai nurse.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 11, Cd OH-01-148, Box 31, Audiocassette 172)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 172)
- Mary Condon, November 2, 1980; cuid45084
  Domestic Worker; Immigration, Ireland.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-045 - OH-01-046)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-045 - OH-01-046)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 28)
- Simm Covington, undated
  NY Transit Authority, SSSA Union.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-242)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-242)
  - Original Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 196)
- Bob Croghan, May 13 and May 20, 2004 (Box 6, Dvd OH-01-489 - OH-01-490)
- Ed Cross, March 20, 1979
  Tunnel Worker Local 147; Job discrimination, minorities.
  - Transcript (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-047 - OH-01-048)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-047 - OH-01-048, Box 23, Audiocassette 29A - 29B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 29A - 29B)
- George Culliman, March 26, 1981
  National Maritime Union.
  - Index (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-243 - OH-01-248)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-243 - OH-01-248)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 30A - 30C)
- Armand D'Angelo, July 22, 1986
  Speaks about Harry van Arsdale.
  - Transcripts (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-436 - OH-01-437)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-436 - OH-01-437)
  - Original Recordings (Box 29, Audiocassette 146 - 146A)
- Frank DaVito, August 28, 1989
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-049)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-049, Box 31, Audiocassette 166)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 166)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_2
- Leonard Difaccio, July 12, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Sebastian Difaccio, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Louis D'Incecco, November 2, 1990
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-249)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-249, Box 31, Audiocassette 183)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 183)
- Domenic DiPaola, January 13, 1994
  Pocketbook Worker, Organization.
  - Notes (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-050 - OH-01-051)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-050 - OH-01-051, Box 33, Audiocassette 218A - 218B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 218A - 218B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_3
- Robert Dobbs, June 20, 1996
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 34, Audiocassette 246)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 246)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_4
- Herbert Dohms, June 2, 1990
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-052)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-052, Box 31, Audiocassette 167)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 167)
- Esther Dolgoff, April 17, 1979
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-053)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-053)
  - Original Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 186)
- Sam Dolgoff, July 2 and July 21, 1981; cuid45085
  Immigration, Eastern European Jewish; Anarchism.
  - Index (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-054 - OH-01-055)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-054 - OH-01-055, Box 24, Audiocassette 31)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 31)
- Thomas Donahue, March 6, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Julius Drumright, July 23, 1974; cuid45086
  Tunnel Workers, Local 147; Job discrimination, minorities.
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-056)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-056)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 32)
- Johnnie Dwyer, November 21, 1980
  International Brotherhood of Longshoremen; file includes many clippings.
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Index (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-057 - OH-01-058)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 8, Cd OH-01-057 - OH-01-058)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 34A - 34B)
- Jeff Eichler, May 18, 1992 and March 8, 1994; cuid36291
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Duration: 96 minutes; digitized recording is in two parts, part "A" (32 minutes) and part "B" (64 minutes).
  United Staff Association of NYU, Local 3882 AFT; clerical and secretarial worker organizing, 1979-1980s.
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-250 - OH-01-251)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-250 - OH-01-251, Box 33, Audiocassette 225A - 225B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 225A - 225B)
- Emmanuel Eisenhandler, October 23, 1990
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 184)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 184)
- Hilliard Ellis African-American trade unionism; UAW/Transport Workers, 1981; cuid45087
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-252 - OH-01-253)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-252 - OH-01-253, Box 23, Audiocassette 35)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 35)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_5
- Ralph Fasenella, June 4, 1981; cuid45088
  United Electrical Workers; McCarthyism.
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Index (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-059 - OH-01-060)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-059 - OH-01-060)
  - Original Recordings (Box 23, Audiocassette 36)
- Charles Fay, April 10, 1986; cuid45089
  United Electrical Workers, Local 475.
  - Transcript (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-061 - OH-01-062)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-061 - OH-01-062, Box 24, Audiocassette 37A - 37B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 37A - 37B)
- Al Filardo, October 10, 1986; cuid45090
  Carpenter; Construction industry, NYC, 1950s-1960s.
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Index (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-063 - OH-01-064)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-063 - OH-01-064)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 38A - 38B)
- Ann Filardo, undated; cuid45152
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Index (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-438 - OH-01-440)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd CDs OH-01-063 - OH-01-064, Box 57, Cd OH-01-438 - OH-01-440)
  - Original Recordings (Box 36, Audiocassette 197A - 197B)
- Jack Finn, July 22, 1981; cuid45091
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-367 - OH-01-369)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-367 - OH-01-369, Box 24, Audiocassette 39A - 39C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 39A - 39C)
- Father Joseph Fitzpatrick, October 12, 1990
  Fordham University.
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 31, Audiocassette 169A - 169D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 169A - 169D)
- Abe Flaxer, April 7, April 23, and May 18, 1981; cuid45092
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Index (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Memoir (Box 43, Folder 4-5)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-485 - OH-01-486)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 12, Cd OH-01-189, Box 58, Cd OH-01-485 - OH-01-486)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 40A - 40D)
- Harry Fleischman, June 8, June 15, and June 23, 1981; cuid45093
  Socialist Party.
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Index (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-254 - OH-01-259)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-254 - OH-01-259, Box 24, Audiocassette 41A - 41D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 41A - 41D)
- Ann Florida, Ann Maitlin, and Zippy Bauman, March 23, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Henry Foner, November 21, 2002; cuid45153
  - Access CDs (Box 17, Cd OH-01-260 - OH-01-261)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-260 - OH-01-261, Box 34, Audiocassette 247A)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 247A)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_6
- Henry Foner and Charles Clair, July 20, 1998; cuid45154
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Index (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-262 - OH-01-263)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-262 - OH-01-263)
  - Original Recordings (Box 34, Audiocassette 247)
- The Ford Farms, undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Maurice Fredericks, April 28 and July 3, 1981; cuid45094
  Brooklyn, CORE; Job discrimination.
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-441 - OH-01-443)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 57, Cd OH-01-441 - OH-01-443, Box 24, Audiocassette 42A - 42C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 42A - 42C)
- Daniel P. French, October 23, 1992; cuid45095
  - Transcript (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 14, Cd OH-01-065)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-065, Box 32, Audiocassette 213)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 213)
- Sam Friedman, February 19, 1986 and January 21, 1990
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-465)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-465, Box 31, Audiocassette 165)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 43A - 43F, Box 39, Audiocassette 165)
- Philoene Fried, daughter of Sidney Hillman, January 12, 1988; cuid45096
  - Transcript (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-066 - OH-01-067)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-066 - OH-01-067, Box 30, Audiocassette 150A - 150B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 150A - 150B)
- Lucy Gallo, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Jimi Gavin National Maritime Union, August 26 and August 29, 1986; cuid45097
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-068 - OH-01-078)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 9, Cd OH-01-068 - OH-01-076, Box 10, Cd OH-01-077 - OH-01-078)
  - Original Recordings (Box 30, Audiocassette 163A - 163F)
- James Garry, March 21, 1989
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 33, Audiocassette 221A - 221B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 221A - 221B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_7
- Bessie Geller, June 29, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Cassette 191A is missing as of Fall 2023.
- Irving Genn, March 29, 1990
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-079 - OH-01-080)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-079 - OH-01-080, Box 16, Audiocassette 164A - 164B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 164A - 164B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_8
- Laviere (Larry) Gentile, December 19, 1996
  Hotel, Restaurant & Club Employees and Bartenders, Local 6.
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-081 - OH-01-082)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-081 - OH-01-082, Box 34, Audiocassette 237A - 237B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 237A - 237B)
- Miriam Gittelson, June 3, 1999; cuid45098
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-083 - OH-01-084)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-083 - OH-01-084, Box 34, Audiocassette 255A - 255B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 255A - 255B)
- John Glasel, June 2, 1993
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 215A - 215B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 215A - 215B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_9
- Thomas Gleason, July 31, 1980; cuid45099
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-085)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-085)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 44)
- Max Goodheim, June 30 and September 21, 1981
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-264 - OH-01-268)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-264 - OH-01-268)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 45A - 45C)
- Michael Goodwin, May 28, 1999
  Immigration, Poland; Pocketbook maker.
  - Notes (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-086)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-086, Box 34, Audiocassette 252)
  - Access Audiocassette (Box 42, Audiocassette 252)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_10
- Lou Gordon, September 10, 1979
  AFL-CIO.
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-269 - OH-01-272)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 53, Cd OH-01-269 - OH-01-271, Box 54, Cd OH-01-272)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 46A - 46C)
- Joseph Gould, December 2, 1989
  Paperworkers, Local 107.
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-087 - OH-01-088)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-087 - OH-01-088, Box 30, Audiocassette 158A - 158B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 158A - 158B)
- Paul Green, September 25, 1992
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-273 - OH-01-275)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-273 - OH-01-275, Box 32, Audiocassette 212A - 212B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 212A - 212B)
- Hy Greenblatt, July 8, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Florence Grogan, October 25, 1996
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-466 - OH-01-467)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-466, Box 33, Audiocassette 236)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 236)
- Paul Hall, 1969; cuid45100
  - Notes (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-491)
  - Original Recordings (Box 24, Audiocassette 47)
- Helmut A. Hallex, March 8 and March 22, 1980
  Seafarers International Union.
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-276 - OH-01-281)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-276 - OH-01-281, Box 24, Audiocassette 48A - 48D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 48A - 48D)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_11
- Gordon Hascal, July 1981 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- James Haughton, October 22, 1980; cuid45101
  - Index (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-089 - OH-01-090)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-089 - OH-01-090, Box 24, Audiocassette 49A - 49B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 49A - 49B)
- James Haughton and Gilbert Banks, October 22, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Peter Hawley, December 6, 1983
  Harlem Fight Back; Job discrimination, minorities.
  - Transcript (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-392 - OH-01-394)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-392 - OH-01-394)
  - Original Recordings (Box 26, Audiocassette 50A - 50B)
- Charles Hayes, July 23, 1981
  United Office & Professional Workers; clerical worker organizing.
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-386)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-386, Box 25, Audiocassette 51)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 51)
- Stan Hill, September 6, 1982
  Black Trade Unionist.
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-322)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 55, Cd OH-01-322)
  - Original Recordings (Box 36, Audiocassette 52)
- Harold Hoffman, February 14, 1985
  AFSCME, District Council 37.
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-468)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-468, Box 30, Audiocassette 161)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 161)
- Walter Hooke, July 16, 1994
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-375 - OH-01-378)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-375 - OH-01-378, Box 33, Audiocassette 223A - 223D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 223A - 223D)
- Ben Holzman, May 17, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  Cassette 53A is missing as of Fall 2023.
- Hudes, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Dolores Huerta, September 4, 1986; cuid45102
  Furniture Workers; Immigration, Poland.
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-091)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-091)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 54)
- Ruth Young Jandreau, August 29, 1985; cuid45158
  - Transcript (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-463 - OH-01-464)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-463 - OH-01-464, Box 32, Audiocassette 217A, Box 33, Audiocassette 217B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 40, Audiocassette 217A, Box 41, Audiocassette 217B)
- Willie Lee Jarrell, March 13, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Sidney Jonas, December 12, 1982; September 3 and September 12, 1983; cuid45103
  United Farm Workers.
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 19, Cd OH-01-357 - OH-01-360)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-357 - OH-01-360, Box 25, Audiocassette 55A - 55D)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 55A - 55D)
- Julie, March 8 and November 15, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-479)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-479, Box 25, Audiocassette 56)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 56)
- Joe Kanowe, October 25, 1988
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-284 - OH-01-285)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-284 - OH-01-285, Box 35, Audiocassette 152A - 152B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 152A - 152B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_12
- Edna Kaplan, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  Cassette 218.5 is missing as of Fall 2023.
- Harry Kelber, June 19, 1980 and July 26, 2006
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-469, OH-01-475)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-469 - OH-01-475, Box 25, Audiocassette 57, Box 35, Audiocassette 263A - 263B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 263A - 263B)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_13
- Theodore Kheel, undated; cuid45104
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Index (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-400)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-400)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 58)
- Ida Klaus, March 10, 1981; cuid45105
  Public Employment Relations Board; "Little Wagner Act".
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Index (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-379 - OH-01-382)
  - Preservation Recordings, cuid43117 (Box 56, Cd OH-01-379 - OH-01-382, Box 25, Audiocassette 59A - 59B)
  - Access Audiocassettes, cuid43118 (Box 36, Audiocassette 59B)
- Jerome Klied, July 17, 1980
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-286 - OH-01-287)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-286 - OH-01-287)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 60)
- Joe Knowles & John Hanbury, September 12, 1985
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-092 - OH-01-094)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-092 - OH-01-094, Box 25, Audiocassette 61A - 61B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 61A - 61B)
- Connie Kopelov, January 29, 1981 and July 14, 1994
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 62A - 62B)
- Kiki Kosut, October 10, 1980
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-095 - OH-01-096)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-095 - OH-01-096)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 63)
- Sam Kovenetsky, November 6 and December 19, 1979
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Index (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-401 - OH-01-402)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-401 - OH-01-402)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 64A - 64B)
- Kitty Krupat, undated; cuid45106
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Access CDs (Box 20, Cd OH-01-403 - OH-01-404)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 56, Cd OH-01-403 - OH-01-404)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 65A - 65D)
- Israel Kugler, December 9, 1995 and April 1, 1997
  - Index (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Original Recordings (Box 33, Audiocassette 229A - 229C, 230)
- Celia Langert, January 23, 1989
  - Access CDs (Box 21, Cd OH-01-480)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 58, Cd OH-01-480, Box 30, Audiocassette 153B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 153B)
- Jesse Langston, July 17, 1982
  - Transcript (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-097 - OH-01-098)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-097 - OH-01-098)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 66)
- Saul Lasher, April 25, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Anita Lathan, September 24, 1999
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 34, Audiocassette 256A)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 256A)
- Oliver Leeds, August 9, 1983
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-288 - OH-01-290)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-288 - OH-01-290, Box 29, Audiocassette 147A - 147C)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 38, Audiocassette 147A - 147C)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_14
- Sarah Leichter, April 26, June 7, and June 21, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Sam & Bessie Levine, October 3, 1980; cuid45107
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Index (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-099 - OH-01-100)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-099 - OH-01-100)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 68A - 68B)
- Barry Lipton, April 2, 1997; cuid45108
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Index (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-101 - OH-01-103)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-101 - OH-01-103, Box 34, Audiocassette 238A - 238B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 238A - 238B)
- George Litsios, June 23, 1994
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-291 - OH-01-292)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-291 - OH-01-292, Box 33, Audiocassette 222A - 222B)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 41, Audiocassette 222A - 222B)
- David Livingston, October 25 and October 30, 1979; cuid45160
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-305 - OH-01-307)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-305 - OH-01-307, Box 12, Cd OH-01-307)
  - Original Recordings (Box 25, Audiocassette 69A - 69C, Box 32, Audiocassette 198A - 198B)
- Ethel Loebman, April 18, 1994
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-293)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-293, Box 35, Audiocassette 153)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 42, Audiocassette 153)
- Cynthia Long, October 19, 1980; cuid45109
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Index (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-108 - OH-01-109)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-108 - OH-01-109)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 25, Audiocassette 70A - 70B)
- Vincent Longhi, December 11, 1993
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Access CDs (Box 18, Cd OH-01-294 - OH-01-295)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 54, Cd OH-01-294 - OH-01-295)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 32, Audiocassette 216A - 216B)
- John Lopez, November 10, 1990
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-104 - OH-01-105)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-104 - OH-01-105, Box 31, Audiocassette 175)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 39, Audiocassette 175)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_15
- Louis Lufkowitz, May 21, 1981
  - Access CDs (Box 15, Cd OH-01-106 - OH-01-107)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 10, Cd OH-01-106 - OH-01-107, Box 25, Audiocassette 67)
  - Access Audiocassettes (Box 36, Audiocassette 67)
  - Transcript, TW_OH_001_ER_16
- John P. Lundergan, April 9, 1991
  - Transcript (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Preservation Recordings (Box 32, Audiocassette 199)